# **JOEL SAUCEDO**

**WEB DEVELOPER** 

ioelcmk@gmail.com Austin, TX

970-331-2807

## **OBJECTIVE**

Proactive, responsible professional seeking a position where I can serve in a team that promotes innovation and entrepreneurship. Despite the fact that I have over five years of experience working in the hospitality business, my passion has been in technology since I was a kid.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**AUSTIN, TX MARCH 2020 - PRESENT** 

#### **Content Moderator**

Accenture

- Assure that users are safe on the platform by removing unwanted content that violates community guidelines.
- Adapt to a fast-changing environment with new technologies, policies, and
- Regularly attend meetings regarding company updates and new technologies.
- Met client satisfaction and expectations by receiving and applying constructive feedback.

AVON, CO September 2014 -November 2018

# **Hospitality**

Westin Hotels

- Communicated the most important updates of the day to coworkers and accordingly allocated and distributed work assignments.
- Supervised the overall activity of eight team members to assure customer satisfaction.
- Communicated with other Westin Hotel departments customer cases that needed to be resolved.

### **EDUCATION**

**ONLINE** 2019 - 2020

# **Coding Bootcamp**

CareerFoundry

Completed an intensive, self-paced program that emphasized technologies required by the expanding tech industry.

Utilized a support network of mentors and tutors to monitor the progress and assure that the program was being successfully completed.

### **LANGUAGES**

**English** 

Spanish: **Native** 

### **SKILLS**

**AWS lambda** HTML CSS **React Native** 

**Javascript** Expo **iQuery Firebase** React Vue.js

Node.Js **Test-Driven Development** 

Mongodb